http://www.tennissolutions.net/terms

Toggle navigation
View Cart (0 Items)
The Player Strap
Nets (2)
Gamma Tennis Nets
Putterman Nets
Racquets
Gamma Racquets (4)
Racquet Stuff (5)
Head Guard
Grips (11)
Replacement Grips
Overgrips (12)
Dampeners (19)
More Racquet Stuff
Training Aids (18)
Court Products
Ballhoppers and Pickups (7)
Net Posts and Net Accessories (8)
Court Valets and Umpire Chairs (9)
Court Benches (10)
Soft Court Equipment (14)
Hard Court Resurfacing (13)
Water Removers (15)
Score Keepers (17)
Windscreens (16)
Balls
GammaTennis Balls (6)
Tennis Solutions
Home of the Slam Strap!
Search
Net Straps
The Slam Strap
The Player Strap
Nets (2)
Gamma Tennis Nets
Putterman Nets
Racquets
Gamma Racquets (4)
Racquet Stuff (5)
Head Guard
Grips (11)
Replacement Grips
Overgrips (12)
Dampeners (19)
More Racquet Stuff
Training Aids (18)
Court Products
Ballhoppers and Pickups (7)
Net Posts and Net Accessories (8)
Court Valets and Umpire Chairs (9)
Court Benches (10)
Soft Court Equipment (14)
Hard Court Resurfacing (13)
Water Removers (15)
Score Keepers (17)
Windscreens (16)
Balls
GammaTennis Balls (6)
Ball Machines
Playmate
Terms & ConditionsPRIVACY POLICYWe take your privacy and security very seriously, and we want you to know how we collect, use, and protect your information.This Privacy Policy tells you:What information we collectHow we use that informationHow we protect your informationYour choices regarding your personal information INFORMATION WE COLLECTInformation You Give UsWe receive and may store any information you enter on our websites, give to us in our stores or provide through our mobile applications. For example, we collect information from you when you place an order, create an account, call us with a question, create a Wish List, write a review, or use any of our services.The information we collect from you includes things like:Your nameYour mailing addressYour e-mail addressYour phone numberYour credit card number and other payment informationYour driver's license numberCredit application information, such as your Social Security numberDemographic and lifestyle information, such as age, personal interests and product preferencesLocation informationIt may also include information you give us about other people, such as the name and address of a gift recipient, or the name and contact info of a Friends & Family Pickup person.Information from Other SourcesWe may also receive information about you from other sources, including third parties that help us update, expand and analyze our records and identify new customers.Public Forums   Our websites offer publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECTWe use the information we collect for things like:Fulfilling orders and requests for products, services or informationProcessing returns, exchanges and layaway requestsTracking and confirming online ordersDelivering or installing productsManaging rewards programsMarketing and advertising products and servicesConducting research and analysisEstablishing and managing your accounts with usCommunicating things like special events, sweepstakes, promotions and surveysOperating, evaluating and improving our businessData RetentionWe will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.HOW WE SHARE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECTTennis Solutions does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties.We may share your information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as:Fulfilling ordersDelivering packagesScheduling and performing installationsServicing productsMaintaining our Reward programsSending Tennis Solutions marketing communicationsFulfilling subscription servicesConducting research and analysisApplying for credit and processing credit card paymentsProviding chat functionsSometimes we may be required to share personal information in response to a regulation, court order or subpoena. We may also share information when we believe it's necessary to comply with the law. We may also share information to respond to a government request or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of Tennis Solutions, our customers, or others; to prevent harm or loss; or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual unlawful activity.We may also share personal information in the event of a corporate sale, merger, acquisition, dissolution or similar event.HOW WE PROTECT THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT We use reasonable security measures to protect the confidentiality of personal information under our control and appropriately limit access to it. Tennis Solutions cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.We use a variety of information security measures to protect your online transactions with us. The Tennis Solutions website uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your personal information during data transport. SSL protects information you submit via our websites such as ordering information, including your name, address and credit card number. Information you provide to us via our in-store kiosk does not traverse the public Internet.YOUR CHOICES REGARDING THE INFORMATION WE COLLECTYou may choose to:Stop receiving marketing or promotional e-mails, direct mail, phone and mobile marketing communicationsUpdate and correct your personal informationCancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you servicesRequest removal of your personal information from our blog or community forumTo do any of these, let us know by one of these methods:Follow the directions in a marketing e-mail or direct mail or mobile communication that you receive from usCall 1-866-238-6552 with your request and current contact informationSend an e-mail with your request and current contact information to:   Slamstrap@gmail.com Send a letter with your request and current contact information to:   Tennis Solutions106 Yahct Basin Landing Hampstead, NC  28443PROTECTING CHILDREN'S PRIVACYWe are committed to protecting children's privacy on the Internet and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITESOur websites link to other websites, many of which have their own privacy policies. Be sure to review the privacy policy on the site you're visiting.PRIVACY POLICY UPDATESWe may need to update our Privacy Policy as Tennis Solutions and our customers grow and evolve. If we make significant changes to the Privacy Policy, we'll post a prominent message on our website(s).If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, we'll do our best to answer them. Here's how to contact us:Phone:866-238-6552E-mail:Slamstrap@gmail.comAddress:Tennis Solutions106 Yacht Basin Landing
View All Products
Home
Shop
Our Story
Contact Us
Terms
Join our email list
Copyright © 2020 Tennis Solutions
